<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
        <string name="terms_content">Last Revised: June 8, 2017\n\n

These Terms of Service (“Terms”) apply to your use of Anon\'s mobile application (the “App”), website (“Site”), and other services (collectively, the “Service”).\n\n

Important:\n
1. Do not post through Anon any of the following:\n
  &#032;• Content that is illegal;\n
  &#032;• Content that may infringe or violate any rights of any party; and\n
  &#032;• Viruses, corrupted data or other harmful, disruptive or destructive files or   code.\n
2. Do not\n
  &#032;• Use Anon if you are not at least 18 years of age. If you are between 13 and 18 years of age, you may only use Anon under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by these terms.\n
  &#032;• Use Anon in any manner that could interfere with, disrupt, negatively affect or inhibit other Anon users or that could damage, disable, overburden or impair the functioning of Anon;\n
  &#032;• Collect any personal information about other users, or intimidate, threaten, stalk or otherwise harass other Anon users;\n
  &#032;• Circumvent or attempt to circumvent any features designed to protect Anon, Anon users, or third parties.\n
3. These Terms are between you and Anon, and not with Apple, Inc. Your use of the Anon Service is governed solely by these terms.\n
4. If you access or use Anon, it means you agree to all the terms below.\n
Accepting these Terms\n
If you access or use the Service, you agree to be bound by all of the terms below. So, before you use the Service, read all of the terms. If you don’t agree to all of the terms below, do not use the Service.\n\n

Changes to Terms:\n
We reserve the right to change the Terms from time to time. For example, we may need to change these Terms if we come out with a new feature. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the Terms and, in some cases, provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Terms of Service periodically to stay informed about our practices. If you continue to use the Service after the revised Terms have been posted, then you have accepted the changes to these Terms.\n
Whenever we make changes to these Terms, they are effective when the revised Terms are posted. If you continue to use the Service after the revised Terms have been posted, then you have accepted the changes to these Terms.\n\n

Privacy Policy:\n
For information about how we collect and use information about users of the Service, please refer to our Privacy Policy.\n\n

Creating accounts:\n
When you create an account you also agree to maintain the security of your password and accept all risks of unauthorized access to your account. If you discover or suspect any Service security breaches, please let us know as soon as possible.\n\n

Minimum Age:\n
By using this service, you represent, acknowledge and agree that you are at least 18 years of age, or if you are under 18 years of age, but are at least 17 years old (a “Minor”), that you have received your parent’s or legal guardian’s permission to use the Services and agree to these Terms. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a Minor, you hereby agree to bind the Minor to these Terms and to fully indemnify and hold harmless Anon if the Minor breaches any of these Terms. If you are not at least 17 years old, you may not use the Services at any time or in any manner or submit any information to the Anon or the Services.\n\n

Right to use the Service\n
Anon grants you a limited, nonexclusive, non-transferable and revocable license to access and use the Service. However, the App may only be used on mobile devices that you own or control. The terms of this license will also govern any upgrades provided by Anon that replace and/or supplement the original App, unless such upgrade is accompanied by a separate license, in which case the terms of that license will govern. However, unless we expressly state otherwise, your right to use the Service does not include (i) publicly performing or publicly displaying the Service, (ii) modifying or otherwise making any derivative uses of the Service or any portion thereof, (iii) using any data mining, robots or similar data gathering or extraction methods, (iv) downloading (other than page caching) of any portion of the Service or any information contained therein, (v) reverse engineering or access to the Service in order to build a competitive product or service, or (vi) using the Service other than for its intended purposes. Should you do any of this, we may terminate your use of the Service, and may have infringed the copyright and other rights of Anon, which may subject you to prosecution and damages.\n
All information, materials and content of the Service including, but not limited to, text, graphics, data, formatting, graphs, designs, HTML, look and feel, photographs, music, sounds, images, software, videos, designs, typefaces, source and object code, format, queries, algorithms and other content is owned by Anon or is used with permission.\n\n

Your content and conduct\n
You agree to follow our Community Guide (and ‘Code of Conduct’). You may not post, link and otherwise make available on or through the Service any of the following:\n
  &#032;• Content that is illegal or unlawful;\n
  &#032;• Content that may infringe or violate any patent, trademark, trade Anon, copyright, right of privacy, right of publicity or other intellectual or other right of any party; and\n
  &#032;• Viruses, corrupted data or other harmful, disruptive or destructive files or code.\n
Also, you agree that you will not do any of the following in connection with the Service or other users:\n
  &#032;• Use the Service in any manner that could interfere with, disrupt, negatively affect or inhibit other users from fully enjoying the Service or that could damage, disable, overburden or impair the functioning of the Service;\n
  &#032;• Collect any personal information about other users, or intimidate, threaten, stalk or otherwise harass other users of the Service;\n
  &#032;• Create an account or post any content if you are not over 13 years of age;\n
  &#032;• Circumvent or attempt to circumvent any filtering, security measures, rate limits or other features designed to protect the Service, users of the Service, or third parties.\n\n

When you post, link or otherwise make available content to the Service, you grant us a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform and display such content throughout the world in any manner or media, on or off the App.\n\n

Feedback:\n
Any suggestions, comments or other feedback provided by you to us with respect to the Service will constitute our confidential information. We will be free to use, disclose, reproduce, license and otherwise distribute, and exploit this feedback as we see fit, entirely without obligation or restriction of any kind on account of intellectual property rights or otherwise.\n
Disclaimers, Limitation of Liability and Indemnification\n
THE SERVICE AND ANY OTHER SERVICE AND CONTENT INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE ARE PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN AS IS OR AS AVAILABLE BASIS WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. WE DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL OTHER WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS (EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ORAL OR WRITTEN) WITH RESPECT TO THE SERVICE AND CONTENT INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE WHETHER ALLEGED TO ARISE BY OPERATION OF LAW, BY REASON OF CUSTOM OR USAGE IN THE TRADE, BY COURSE OF DEALING OR OTHERWISE. IN NO EVENT WILL ANON BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICE OR ANY OTHER SERVICE AND CONTENT INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE, REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR ARE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.\n\n

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold us harmless from and against any and all costs, damages, liabilities, and expenses (including attorneys’ fees) we incur we in relation to, arising from, or for the purpose of avoiding, any claim or demand from a third party that your use of the Service or the use of the Service by any person using your account violates any applicable law or regulation, or the rights of any third party, and/or your violation of these Terms.\n\n

Third Party Software:\n
The software you download consists of a package of components, including certain third party software (“Third Party Software” and together with the App, the “Package”) provided under separate license terms (the “Third Party Terms”). Your use of the Third Party Software in conjunction with the App in a manner consistent with the terms of these Terms is permitted, however, you may have broader rights under the applicable Third Party Terms and nothing in these Terms is intended to impose further restrictions on your use of the Third Party Software.\n\n

Modifications to the Service\n
Anon reserves the right in its sole discretion to review, improve, modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service and/or any features, information, materials or content on the Service with or without notice to you. You agree that Anon will not be liable to you or any third party for any modification or discontinuance of the Service or any portion thereof.\n\n

Consent to Electronic Communications:\n
By using the Service, you agree that any communications that we send to you electronically will satisfy any legal requirements, including that such communications be in writing. To withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice, please notify us at anontheapp@gmail.com.\n\n

Suspension/Termination\n
Anon may suspend and/or terminate your rights with respect to the Service for any reason or for no reason at all and with or without notice at Anon’s sole discretion. Suspension and/or termination may include restricting access to and use of the App. If your rights with respect to the Service are suspended and/or terminated, you agree to make no further use of the Service during suspension or after termination. All of the terms of these Terms (excluding the license grant) will survive any termination or suspension.\n
If Anon believes a Post you have made violates these Terms, Anon may make that Post invisible to all users without notifying you.\n\n

Governing Law; Arbitration\n
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PARAGRAPHS CAREFULLY BECAUSE THEY REQUIRE YOU TO ARBITRATE DISPUTES WITH ANON AND LIMIT THE MANNER IN WHICH YOU CAN SEEK RELIEF FROM ANON.\n\n

In the event of any controversy or claim arising out of or relating in any way to these Terms or the Service, you and Anon agree to consult and negotiate with each other and, recognizing your mutual interests, attempt to reach a solution satisfactory to both parties. If we do not reach settlement within a period of 60 days, then either of us may, by notice to the other demand mediation under the mediation rules of South Africa. We both give up our right to litigate our disputes and may not proceed to arbitration without first attempting mediation, except that you and Anon are NOT required to arbitrate any dispute in which either party seeks equitable and other relief from the alleged unlawful use of copyrights, trademarks, trade names, logos, trademarks or patents. Whether the dispute is heard in arbitration or in court, you and Anon will not commence against the other a class action, class arbitration or other representative action or proceeding.\n\n

If settlement is not reached within 60 days after service of a written demand for mediation, any unresolved controversy or claim will be resolved by arbitration in accordance with the relevant legal rules of arbitration before a single arbitrator in Johannesburg, South Africa. The language of all proceedings and filings will be English. The arbitrator will render a written opinion including findings of fact and law and the award and/or determination of the arbitrator will be binding upon the parties, and their respective administrators and assigns, and will not be subject to appeal. Judgment may be entered upon the award of the arbitrator in any court of competent jurisdiction. The expenses of the arbitration will be shared equally by the parties unless the arbitration determines that the expenses will be otherwise assessed and the prevailing party may be awarded its attorneys\' fees and expenses by the arbitrator.\n\n

It is the intent of the parties that, barring extraordinary circumstances, arbitration proceedings will be concluded within 90 days from the date the arbitrator is appointed. The arbitrator may extend this time limit only if failure to do so would unduly prejudice the rights of the parties. Failure to adhere to this time limit will not constitute a basis for challenging the award.\n\n

Consistent with the expedited nature of arbitration, pre-hearing information exchange will be limited to the reasonable production of relevant, non-privileged documents, carried out expeditiously.\n\n

Copyright Policy\n
a. Notice.\n
If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that any content available on our Service infringes your copyrights, you may, pursuant to the Copyright Act 98 of South Africa ("CASA"), notify our Copyright Agent via anontheapp@gmail.com. Please include:\n
  &#032;• A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;\n
  &#032;• Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;\n
  &#032;• Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material;\n
  &#032;• Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact you, such as an address, telephone number and, if available, an electronic mail;\n
  &#032;• A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and\n
  &#032;• A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.\n\n

You acknowledge that a failure to comply with all of the above requirements will result in an invalid notification.\n
Anon, Inc.’s designated Copyright Agent to receive notifications of claimed infringement is:\n
Anon CASA Agent\n
Email: anontheapp@gmail.com\n\n

b. Counter-Notice.\n
If you believe that your content that was removed (or to which access was disabled) is not infringing, or that you have the authorization from the copyright owner, the copyright owner’s agent or pursuant to other law, to submit the content to Anon, you may send a counter-notice containing the following information to the Copyright Agent:\n
  &#032;• Your physical or electronic signature;\n
  &#032;• Identification of the content that was removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the content appeared before it was removed or disabled;\n
  &#032;• A statement that you have a good faith belief that the content was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or a misidentification of the content; and\n
  &#032;• Your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address and a statement that you will accept service of process from the person who provided notification of the alleged infringement.\n
If a counter-notice is received by the Copyright Agent, Anon may send a copy of the counter-notice to the original complaining party informing that person that it may replace the removed content or cease disabling it in 10 business days. Unless the copyright owner files an action seeking a court order against the content provider, member, or user, the removed content may be replaced, or access to it restored, in 10 to 14 business days or more after receipt of the counter-notice, at Anon’s sole discretion.\n\n

NOTICE REGARDING APPLE\n
While you may be subject to certain terms and conditions with Apple, Inc. by using Apple’s App Store or other products, these Terms are specifically between You and Anon. Your use of the Anon Service is governed solely by these terms.\n\n

Notwithstanding any terms to the contrary in these Terms, the following additional terms will apply to the download of the App for use on the iPhone, iPod Touch or iPad:\n\n

You and Anon acknowledge that the terms are solely between you and Anon, and not with Apple, Inc. (“Apple”), and that Anon, not Apple, is solely responsible for the Service, the content thereof, maintenance, support services and warranty therefor, and addressing any claims relating thereto (e.g., product liability, legal compliance or intellectual property infringement).\n\n

You acknowledge and agree that the availability of the App is dependent on the third party from which you received the App, e.g., the Apple iPhone App Store (“App Store”).\n\n

You agree to pay all fees charged by the App Store in connection with the App (if any).\n\n

You further acknowledge that the usage rules for the App are subject to any additional restrictions set forth in the Usage Rules for the Apple App Store Terms of Service as of the date you download the App. In the event of any conflict between the terms and conditions of the Usage Rules for the Apple App Store Terms of Service and the terms and conditions of these Terms, the terms and conditions of the Usage Rules for the Apple App Store Terms of Service will govern if they are more restrictive.\n\n

Scope of License:\n
The license granted to you is limited to a non-transferable license to use the App on any iPhone, iPod Touch or iPad that you own or control as permitted by the Usage Rules set forth in the Apple App Store Terms of Service.\n
Maintenance and Support\n
Anon is solely responsible for providing maintenance and support services with respect to the App.\n\n

You acknowledge and agree that Apple has no obligation whatsoever to furnish any maintenance and support services with respect to the App.\n\n

Warranty:\n
You acknowledge and agree that Apple is not responsible for any product warranties, whether express or implied by law, with respect to the App. In the event of any failure of the App to conform to any applicable warranty, you may notify Apple, and Apple will refund the purchase price, if any, paid to Apple for the App by you; and to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Apple will have no other warranty obligation whatsoever with respect to the App. You also acknowledge and agree that to the extent that there are any applicable warranties, or any other claims, losses, liabilities, damages, costs or expenses attributable to any failure to conform to any such applicable warranty, such will be the sole responsibility of Anon. However, you understand and agree that in accordance with these Terms, Anon has disclaimed all warranties of any kind with respect to the App, and therefore, there are no warranties applicable to the App, except those implied by law.\n\n

Product Claims:\n
You and Anon acknowledge and agree that as between Apple and Anon, Anon, not Apple, is responsible for addressing any of your claims or any third party claims relating to the App or your possession and/or use of the App, including, but not limited to: (i) product liability claims; (ii) any claim that the App fails to conform to any applicable legal or regulatory requirement; and (iii) claims arising under consumer protection or similar legislation.\n
 Intellectual Property Rights\n
You and Anon acknowledge and agree that, in the event of any third party claim that the App or your possession and use of the App infringes that third party’s intellectual property rights, Anon, and not Apple, will be solely responsible for the investigation, defense, settlement and discharge of any such intellectual property infringement claim to the extent required under these Terms.\n\n

Legal Compliance:\n
You represent and warrant that: (i) you are not located in a country that is subject to a South Africa Government embargo, or that has been designated by the South African Government as a “terrorist supporting” country; and (ii) you are not listed on any South African Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.\n
Developer Name and Address\n
Any end-user questions, complaints or claims with respect to the App should be directed to:\n
Anon, Ltd\n
Email: anontheapp@gmail.com\n\n

Third Party Beneficiary:\n
The parties acknowledge and agree that Apple, and Apple’s subsidiaries, are third party beneficiaries of these Terms, and that, upon your acceptance of the terms and conditions of these Terms, Apple will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce any of the terms and conditions of these Terms against you as a third party beneficiary thereof.</string>


    <string name="privacy_contents">Last Revised: June 8, 2017\n\n

This privacy policy explains how Anon, Inc. (“Anon,” “we,” “us” or “our”) collects, uses and discloses information about you when you use our mobile application (the “App”), our Web site (the “Site”) and other online products and services that link to this privacy policy (collectively, the “Service”). By using the Service, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.\n\n

Through the Service, you can anonymously share posts (“Anons”) with other users of the Service. \n\n

Modifications:\n
We may change this privacy policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we will provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the privacy policy periodically to stay informed about our practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.\n
 Collection of Information:\n
 Information You Provide to Us\n
We collect information you directly give us. For example, we collect information about you when you make a Anon, give feedback about the Service or otherwise communicate with us.\n
 The types of information we may collect includes your email address, your mobile phone number and any other information you choose to provide. \n
Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Service:\n
 When you access or use our Service, we automatically collect certain information about you. This information includes:\n
  &#032;• Log Information: We log information about your use of the Service, including access times, location information, and Posts viewed. We use this information for analytic and product improvement purposes.\n
  &#032;• Device Information: We may collect information about the mobile device you use to access our Service, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information. We use this information for analytic and product improvement purposes.\n
  &#032;• Location Information: We may collect information about the general location of your Internet Service Provider based on your IP Address. If you allow Anon to access your location information, we may also collect your geolocation information. We use this information to show you Anons from users in your Network who are located near you and to show your Anons to users in your Network who are nearby. For information as to how to restrict the collection of geolocation information, please see the “Your Choices” section below.\n
  &#032;• Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We may use various technologies to collect information, and this may include cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory. Web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”) are non-visible electronic images.   These technologies are used for analytic and product improvement purposes, such as seeing which areas and features of our Service are popular and determining whether an email has been opened and acted upon. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.\n
 Use of Information:\n
We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:\n
  &#032;• Provide, deliver, maintain, test and improve our Service;\n
  &#032;• Send you technical notices, updates, confirmations, security alerts and support and administrative messages;\n
  &#032;• Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;\n
  &#032;• Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by Anon and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;\n
  &#032;• Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Service and improve and personalize the Service;\n
  &#032;• Detect, investigate and prevent any suspected breaches of our Terms of Service; and\n
  &#032;• Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and\n
 Storage of Information:\n
We take reasonable measures to protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, but we cannot guarantee that our system is infallible.\n
 We also seek to minimize the data we keep. We seek to store your information only as long as necessary to accomplish the purposes described in this privacy policy.\n
 Sharing of Information:\n
We may share aggregated, de-identified or non-personal information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this privacy policy:\n
  &#032;• With other users of the Service by providing them with your Anons and your general location (if you have enabled us to collect your location).\n
We may also share information about you as follows:\n
  &#032;• With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;\n
  &#032;• In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Anon assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company;\n
  &#032;• In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;\n
  &#032;• If the content of a Anon can reasonably be considered illegal or unlawful (or we have a good faith belief that such Anon is being used to engage in, encourage or promote such activities), in which case we may share your identity and other information with proper authorities;\n
  &#032;• If we believe that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate in order to protect the rights, property and safety of Anon, our users and/or others; and\n
  &#032;• With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Service that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.\n
Note that if you choose to include information about you in your Anons, such information will be shared with other users of the Service who receive such Anons as described in this privacy policy. We suggest that you do not include any identifiable information about you in your Anons.   Also, please note that if you or other users choose to share content through a third party, such as Facebook, Twitter or an email client, any further collection and sharing of that content by such third party or its users will be governed by that third party’s privacy policy, and we cannot control what any third party does with any content or other information that is shared with third parties.\n
 How We Respond to Subpoenas from Courts:\n
If a court asks us to disclose your identity, we may be compelled to do so to the extent possible.\n
 International Users:\n
Anon is based in South Africa and the information we collect is governed by SA law. By accessing or using the Service or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to SA and other countries.   Information shared in accordance with this privacy policy may be disclosed to recipients in SADEC (The Southern African Development Community) countries and/or overseas recipients located in the United States, Canada, the European Union, Australia and New Zealand and other African countries. This may include disclosures to other African and overseas recipients outside of the SADEC region, including countries that do not have laws that protect personal information in the same manner as countries within the SADEC region.\n
 Analytics Services Provided by Others:\n
We may allow third parties to provide analytics services to us. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Service, including your IP address, Anons, Anons viewed, time spent on Anons, and Anon information. This information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity.\n
 Your Choices:\n
 Cookies\n
Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your web browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Removing or rejecting browser cookies does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in connection with the Service. To delete or disable flash cookies please visit www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security for more information. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Service.\n
 Push Notifications and Alerts\n
With your consent, we may send push notifications or alerts to your mobile device. You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your mobile device.\n
 Contact Information\n
You can restrict Anon’s collection of contacts by changing your phone’s privacy settings. On iPhone, go to Settings > Privacy > Contacts and switch Anon to “Off.”\n
 Geolocation Information\n
You can restrict Anon’s collection of geolocation information by changing your phone’s privacy settings. On iPhone, go to Settings > Privacy > Location, and switch Anon to “Off.”\n
 Contact Us:\n
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy or any privacy issues, please email us at anontheapp@gmail.com\n
    </string>


</resources>